[Music]
To give a high five, you need one more
person. Come, let me show you the other
half of the story.
Welcome to the 48 hour challenge, where
we close one case within 48 hours upon
joining.
>> Close.
>> Who's the clan?
>> My mother. Always
protect your family first. Now let's see
how we train you.
>> They say it self is a soft skill, but
there's nothing soft here.
>> Yes, sir.
[Music]
>> Yes. Good.
>> Uh hi. Uh, may may I just follow up with
you? A gentle reminder to follow up.
>> Don't sound so desperate.
>> What do you do when they say they
already have interest?
>> Ask for their friends contact.
>> What do you do when they say they want
to think about it?
>> Think with them until they say yes.
>> What do you do when they say they have
no money?
>> Call them when salary comes out.
Salespeople are not born, they are made.
Ready to see what's next?
[Music]
[Applause]
>> Thank you FWD for giving me the platform
to become MDRT.
[Music]
>> Can you share with us how you qualify
for MDRT?
From day one, I'm already MBRT mentally.
>> Dare to dream.
Oh, let's see what's next.
[Music]
>> Client thinks I'm in office.
>> Freedom to choose.
To give a high five, you need one more
person. But who says you have to stop at
one?
[Music]
In FWD, you can have it all.